kaust.edu.sa 2015-12-27

# Privacy Policy | King Abdullah University of Science and Technology (KAUST)

## KING ABDULLAH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY PRIVACY POLICY

This Policy was last updated in March, 2009. 

King Abdullah University of Science and Technology (KAUST) is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with this Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information KAUST collects through the KAUST website (the "Website") and does not apply to information KAUST collects in any other manner. Your use of the Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and KAUST's Terms of Use [insert link]. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how KAUST treats information collected through the Website.

## Collection and Retention of Information

In some areas of the Website, such as when you submit an application for admission or apply for a job with KAUST, request information, or register for an event, KAUST may request that you provide personal information, including, as applicable, your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your unique identity is discernible. In other areas of the Website, KAUST collects or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your country of residence, age, level of education, gender, and other similar types of information. Sometimes KAUST collects or may collect a combination of these two types of information.

KAUST also gathers or may gather certain information about your use of the Website, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. In addition, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by KAUST. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.

In order to maintain your information in an efficient manner, KAUST retains the information it gathers about you to make your repeat visits to the Website more efficient, practical, and relevant.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

KAUST does not disclose to third parties your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of the Website (such as the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth in the following subparagraphs.

  * KAUST may disclose such information to companies and individuals KAUST works with in carrying out its functions, including companies and individuals authorized to perform functions on its behalf. Examples may include hosting its Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, assisting with recruitment, collaborating with education and research, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions.
  * KAUST may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if it believes in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of KAUST; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
  * KAUST may also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to the Website with its partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors that visit the KAUST site and how those visitors use the site.

In the event that KAUST contracts with a third party to provide some part of the information or service that you have requested, KAUST may provide your information to such third party, or such third party may collect information from you on KAUST's behalf. KAUST uses reliable service providers who undertake to put in place appropriate security measures to ensure a reasonable level of protection. Such third parties will have access to personal information solely for the purposes of performing the services for which they have been engaged.

## Updating Your Information

If you registered or created a profile on the Website, you may correct or update the information you provided to KAUST at any time by contacting the KAUST Digital team.

If you request to receive newsletters or other communications from KAUST, but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the e-news alert e-mails or by e-mailing theKAUST Digital team. If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by re-subscribing to the e-news alert through the Register for News Updates registration form.

## Security

KAUST maintains appropriate technical, physical, and organizational measures to protect personal information against unauthorized access, unlawful processing, accidental loss or damage, and unauthorized destruction. However, KAUST cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

## Links to Other Sites

The Website contains links to third-party websites that are provided for your convenience. KAUST does not endorse nor is it responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies and terms of use that govern those websites when you visit them.

## Children

The Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age, and KAUST does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

KAUST reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by KAUST on this Website. If KAUST makes any material changes to the manner in which your personal information will be used under this Privacy Policy, you will be notified of such changes and will be given the opportunity to object to such new or different use. Such modifications will be denoted by the "last updated" notice at the top of this page. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates or changes. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.

## Contact Information

We welcome your comments concerning this Privacy Policy. If at any time, you have questions about KAUST's Privacy Policy, please contact the KAUST Marketing Communication.
